# VERONIKA KLOSOVYCH

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER



# CONTACT

778-712-2512

nicole.klosovich@gmail.com



Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada



LinkedIn



GitHub

# SKILLS

- HTML/HTML5
- CSS/CSS3, Sass/SCSS
- JavaScript/ES6, TypeScript
- React.js, Vue.js
- Backbone.js, Marionette, Handlebars
- Bootstrap, Foundation
- Git (GitLab & GitHub)
- Node.js, Express.js
- Unit Testing (Jest, Mocha, Storybook)
- AJAX, JQuery, JSON
- Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner

# EDUCATION

### FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT COURSE

Main Academy **2020** 

#### **MASTERS IN INTERNATIONAL ECONOMICS**

Kyiv National Economics University named after Vadym Hetman

2014 - 2020

## PROFILE

I am an experienced front-end developer more than 2 years of professional experience working for US-based clients.

Additionally, my experience collaborating with designers, developers, and other stakeholders has helped me develop strong communication skills and a collaborative mindset.

# EXPERIENCE

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

**Grid Dynamics** 

2021 - Present

- Working as Frontend Developer for Grid Dynamics' client Macy's
- Implementing new website features, improving website CLS
- Fixing various types of software bugs concerning user interface

#### FRONEND DEVELOPER INTERN

**Grid Dynamics** 

2021

- Solving algorithm problems
- Working on capstone project e-commerce website, using TypeScript, React and Material UI Framework.

#### MARKETING MANAGER

Infopulse Ukraine

2019 - 2020

- Doing market research, analyzing competitor's products and services
- Compiling and analyzing statistical data, assess future trends
- Making recommendations for business development